I'll call it over to the regular scheduled meeting of my city council from Monday, August 7, 2020.
Public input on schedule personal answers. We have nine. Three claims.
What's your proof?
Second.
What do you say?
Hi.
So what?
Williams.
Hi.
Son of a.
Parker.
Hi.
Four minutes for the July 17th.
Regger's scheduled meeting in July 24th.
Regger's scheduled meeting for the State Special.
No, that is a work session.
Regger.
Motion approved.
Second.
Hi.
Each set of Williams.
Son of a.
Hi.
Parker.
Five budget amendment.
Number 23-28.
Fire using unbended CPR card revenue to reimburse for its own expense.
The cost is, and the budget for a certain number of cards that they had more
parts been anticipated for this is that you've read the report that you've built
the list with.
Outside organization contracts for fiscal year 23-294 for Miami senior senior, senior centers.
Community crisis center, grain gateway to Pennsylvania, and Miami area, economic development
at the Oregon Foundation.
the senior center, community courses, and relevant,
they use the same template for the contract.
So the changes are the dates,
and the financial statements calling instead of every time
they ask for reimbursement,
that also allows you to promote any of the such expressions
such as those that came to you on time,
ask for share of it.
It is what we did last year impact the week in the city bank court.
Did we approve all the amounts and these in budget time I think we had questions on some of these in
That's what we had them come in and speak
In present for the grand gateway for the Pelven primarily the one and then they're gonna come back again
And then speak because they've got some
Operational updates that they're excited about they're gonna come speak
So we did do that last year we did a study session at this senior center and then last year. We taught study set
Pelven was one way
Pelven was the one we we weren't sure about just because they had a local office and then they had sold that local office, so we had them come in and explain
What what they were doing why that it's so old and how they're continuing to operate and what their numbers were
That was the last meeting the meeting before meeting the last one was our study session
So I'll be honest. I didn't get much out of that meeting for the end of the day
I don't think those did it would make me feel any better about it
I would prefer to pull that one out. We'll prove the other three
For me until they come back and we all get a chance to talk to them
I was here and they talked
Do we lump all these together normally that
No last three your motion you can
Well, now last year whenever we've had to see your citizens in or we talked about
The amount of people that they served and it was just that it was just really a handful and
Did you get anything out of it this time as far as it's it's it's they're serving any more people and then what they were
I think whenever we whenever we were out here though, we've like in coping times and post-COVID
They were still in regaining their numbers, but are one any numbers. Yeah, what any numbers close to that?
I think they are, because they have a thing face, like if the same person comes to dinner to say,
but it's what they said.
Counting the number of times, they serve the public.
Yeah.
Did we, did they get a count on meals, did that, that increase?
That's part.
We can have dogs.
Dogs are so different.
Dogs are part of that.
Mitten.
It's like a man.
Well, they were making meals there weren't they?
Was that dogs are making the meals?
Makes sense of they served.
Yeah.
That's part of the presentation.
That's the same.
Well, actually we have dogs as one group.
We have no pet present.
We've had no mob in that group.
We speak to the council, but not dogs.
How does the contract with dogs work?
Is that?
So, Matt, you know, how many of us have 15, 16?
The men's city manager and dogs lost their federal funding for rent.
They were giving the senior center a thousand months.
And that's also the presentation.
Well, last year we talked about the kind of looking at that again this year on how much
A.S. urban stuff and I think we talked about the meals as well.
But, and then, you know, looking and seeing if we're going to subsidize the same or
a little less and then kind of be on there.
They're costs have gone up, which is primarily what they've been sharing with us.
There needs to go up with their building, aging, things that nature.
So I know that they had came to us and talked about that.
But I don't think they presented necessarily a new number to the same one that's last year.
Hello.
Hello, your president.
I'm not.
So, um, am I hearing that we would like for some of these folks to come talk to us before we, okay, this?
How long have we been subsidizing?
I'm just subsidizing how we do something different with them.
I actually have our building.
The community crisis centers and fellow men, senior center, coursemates.
We talked about small business development, boys and girls stuff.
Personally, I'd like to talk more to fellow men people to the.
Let's go with the seniors here.
You're getting the seniors here.
Everybody else.
Hi, guys.
Yeah.
I'm going to be going to be a crisis and maybe just a little bit.
Everybody.
Yeah.
I agree with that.
So I'll make a motion.
We improve the contrast with monoceneor center.
I mean, a crisis center.
And maids.
And we'll pull up and get what we call man to the intelligence.
Take it.
Go ahead.
Hi.
7th.
Williams.
Hi.
So.
Thank you.
7th.
Claire.
Okay.
Wionn Radio.
Equipment surplus.
And approve.
Foundation to create county sheriff work.
This year.
I'm going for the first new radius.
So for everybody else.
They did that through funds.
Our funds through all of them.
And everybody.
every place, fire, definitely, everybody has a right of right now.
We've been using our Oakland Radio's, which is the state system for about 20 years.
Like, that system came out.
I don't know whether that was a little bit quiet,
but it was going to be our building.
Most of our radio's are day-to-back.
Most of the state's still on that system.
For auto-canning, there's a totally useful sound.
So, Craig County still uses the Oakland system.
So, we just want to provide them some of our circles where it is.
There are no use to anybody in auto-canning,
because we all went to endless systems,
but we're just going to want you to have a better radio to our balance.
Once we're fully operational, one of the best systems.
I see, is that a fact that radio tower out there on the 90, 90-row?
We did put it on the channel, I guess.
The city owns that.
We put the radio antenna, the horn, the fire iron,
so the opening will all be any longer.
Make a motion.
We approve.
Take it.
Hi.
Hey.
It's the pair of 2014 Ford Explorer surplus
and a pre-donation to the Senate.
The police department and the town of the Senate.
We do this.
I want to go back.
So, we did the parallel.
Last year, we had to put about one.
Then give it back.
We had to go back.
This car has been straight.
I had to say the car on right and here.
They're cheating back to quality for a light bar.
And I said, a picture of us that have got one in a car much ground.
It's a test of car.
It takes a lot of time.
But that's a car too.
But what if your car's on your back?
This is our dark car.
On the TNM vehicle, we have to fill the guttings here for a whole K-Zone.
So we don't have a car to make it a place car.
And honestly, we're on the TNM every couple of years,
and there's no people riding in it.
I just thought of essence.
And no one's far.
So if we can go here and have a running.
And if you can be used to an apartment, we...
I'm sorry, I'll make a motion to a break.
Wait a second.
Hi.
This guy's an assistant.
He's going to come in handy on Shuttle Syrians doing this.
So he can just use his assistant to a 2.5-hour nap axe.
Darn you getting it in there from a six-fifth5 passenger.
I add.
He can place his assistant to a five-hour nap axe.
So I just use a six-fifth5 passenger.
I think around in the cooking field.
Just pick up some extra stuff.
And then I, we came together.
On your head with your foot, and your hand, and forth.
I still have one next.
Now, if this was a high area of accidents, speedy complaints, track violations about an
absolute sense, maybe I can't back up any other than, I guess, the one citizen's complaining.
In either location, we ran number for a couple of years, and there are no statistical data that
I actually know that people have lived at the corner of 7th and 8th on the west, and the stops on the east side
in there yard, and I asked them what they thought about it, and they absolutely did not want to
always stop there.
So, they requested that we would not have been able to share that concern, and I told them
what I was looking at.
I was looking at us, but it was always true, you know.
They should have gone back to the stats, I don't have any to go back.
I was the one that got called on the, well, he called the sheriff, the sheriff called me off on me,
it's 1100 in northwest.
He was compliant because he's got a lot of kids running around that neighborhood, and he called me.
And he's pups.
Well, they all got a lot of kids in the neighborhood.
I'm just telling them what they said.
And there are several intersections that we know of what I'd like to have, but we're under control.
I'm going to still pause and cover that.
They're just so, such a scary insects, they're not a wild trap, and we just never had an issue.
Good enough.
Give me another question.
Chief.
Thank you.
10.
How the new business of any, which is the results of the posting of this agenda.
11 staff reports.
12 mayor council committee announcements.
Right again.
I know he's looking at too.
Sure.
Oh, Jennifer happy birthday.
I mean, I'm sure you're going to talk about the last week he ran, right?
That's pretty much all I have to talk about.
He was a great time.
Way to get time.
I thought he went very well.
I don't know what the numbers are.
The interest is now how he did compared to the past years.
I think they're pretty good.
From my understanding, we haven't had to follow me.
I think it's this week.
Thursday.
So we'll know a little more than that.
But I'd say Sharon's back with us.
Sharon had a little heat problem.
And it's been a couple days in the hospital.
So we're glad he's back from the healthy.
Well, I don't know.
It's back.
I'm here.
But it was a good event.
Two of those to the city staff from pop the bottom.
You got to do a great job.
Your people did a great job.
They pulled this off and made it happen.
Excellent communication.
It was just going around the green.
Great.
We just got to show up and have fun.
It was in the middle of the rest.
But our city staff is top and off.
We appreciate each and every one of you for putting in your time.
And I was hot.
And there's a lot of people down there.
We know we had a lot of former ward offs back and down.
That we're really having a good time.
And that we're really like and not only in the event.
But with a community look like again,
Kudos to your people for their work every day.
We've paid off when these people came home.
Okay.
It's real impressive to see that come together because it starts.
You know, weeks weeks in advance.
Like a crew and a parks crew and all of them.
I'm trying to make sure that the timing is just right.
That they get everything done and looking really good for that weekend.
And they do a great job.
I'm dressed me.
I'm driving around and looking and holding my time.
I hope they get that corner.
I hope they get that all out.
They get it.
And it does.
They actually all think it's done.
They've over the last three years.
They've just got it the end of the science.
And so it works great.
Everything looked great.
It couldn't have been well proud.
The flipping of the stage worked beautifully.
That was probably the biggest change.
Maybe a little bit of concern we had.
Do any of you just how's that going to work?
Went great.
I heard nothing like great.
Everybody loved the stage or in the location.
How do I have it?
And now closer to the colon.
It worked well for the VIP.
We didn't have to have two of them.
So it produced our cost.
Certainly like that.
It just worked well.
Well, in the barbecue did great.
Down there at the other end.
The other end.
Those guys, you know, Shannon had that thing, some organize, yeah, so we're gonna, you went there and it's still arranged.
Those guys were so impressed with Shannon.
They just went on and on and on.
They love Shannon for sure.
They were very concerned about you, and that they were gonna have the trophy just up.
Well, they were gonna let us get out trophies.
They did.
Yeah, they were more concerned about you than the trophies in the body.
They were.
They were impressed, and that's great, because that means they'll be back.
So it, that'll continue to be a successful event for us.
But yeah, you know, the marketplace seemed to be, have more people participating in the past.
So it seemed very full.
I like that, I like that everything was on Main Street, and we didn't stick all the food trucks off on the side streets.
And I thought that was better visibility, and I think it was better for them.
I think that worked well.
It took me up chicks up here.
So the Center worked out well, and it was great.
Activity appeared.
Yeah.
I've heard their numbers to see how they did it.
Most of them are most all day Saturday, and there was people in the whole day.
Okay.
My wife was there three out.
Just going through the steps.
So there's lots to see.
For the car show, by show, well.
You know, and we're thinking of PD in our fire department.
We didn't have a whole lot of issues with the need.
We had people that I think we had to get cooled off and cooled down and hydrated.
We had no serious incidents, health related incidents.
And I don't think we had any disturbances.
So people really behave themselves.
We had to do the show.
Other major coaches are in box and we had to be able to do a little bit of the changes.
Yeah.
How are you?
One health related incident.
Other than that, great event.
I can't say enough about staff.
And everybody pulling together.
Make it happen.
Absolutely takes.
And the thing about this event too is this, it's turned into rain and weekend.
For not only miles out of regions there, but commerce.
Even had a rain in there this year.
And then those guys that had a rain in the last year enjoyed it so much.
They came back this year.
So because they want to see the classes before and after them.
So it's starting to be where it's the weekend for everybody to come home.
Which is kind of cool.
You can see a lot of people we have seen a long time.
I saw some people this year that I hadn't seen in 25 or 30 years.
Yes.
And so it's kind of cool.
But they recognize you on Facebook.
And...